Guide to the Louis H. Roddis Papers, 1823-1990 RL.01102
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Detroit Edison Series, 1972-1987 and undated (bulk 1982-1987)
  Includes audit reports, cost histories, meetings' agendas and minutes, correspondence, printed materials, testimonies, rebuttals, computer lists, and reports. This series contains Detroit Edison's Board of Director's Nuclear Review Committee's research findings on the rationalization of raising its Fermi-2 reactor's budget from $228 million in 1974 to $3 billion in 1984 and the safety of the reactor. Roddis served as Chairman on Detroit Edison's Board of Directors.
  - Fermi 2 Michigan Public Service Commission (MPSC) Staff Preliminary Audit Report, 1984 Feb. 27 (volume) (Box 54)
  - An Analysis of the Michigan Public Service Commission Staff Investigation of Enrico Fermi 2 Nuclear Power Project Dated February 1984, 1984 June (volume) (Box 54)
  - The Detroit Edison Company Rebuttal--Case No. U-7660 Exhibits, undated (volume) (Box 54)
  - Fermi 2--Final Assessment of Construction, 1984 Jul. (volume) (Box 55)
  - Cost History, 1984 Apr. 3, 5 folders (Box 55)
  - Fermi 2 Masterlist of Construction Items Waiting to be Completed, 1984 Dec., 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Sale of Fermi 2 Between the Detroit Edison Companyand Wolverine Power Supply Cooperative, 1977 Feb. 8 (volume) (Box 55)
  - Presentation to the Nuclear Review Committee (NRC) Board of Directors, 1987 Oct. (Box 55)
  - Detroit Edison Nuclear Safety Review Group (NSRG) 91-02, 1991 Mar. 21 (4 volumes) (Box 55)
  - Nuclear Safety Review Group, 1985-1986 (Box 55)
  - NRC, 1985-1986 (Box 55)
  - NRC Meeting, 1985 Nov. (Box 56)
  - NRC Meeting, 1985 Oct. (Box 56)
  - Minutes of NSRG Meeting of July 18-19, 1985; 1985 Sept. (Box 56)
  - NRC Meeting, 1985 Jun. (Box 56)
  - NRC/NSRG, 1985, June-July (Box 56)
  - NRC Meeting, 1985 May (Box 56)
  - Detroit Edison NRC Minutes, 1985 (Box 56)
  - NSRG Meeting Minutes, 1985 Jan. 17-18 (Box 56)
  - NRC Meeting, 1985 May (Box 56)
  - NRC Meeting, 1985 Mar. (Box 56)
  - NRC Meeting, 1985 Jan.-Mar. (Box 56)
  - NRC Meeting on Jan. 28, 1985; 1985 Jan.-Feb. (Box 56)
  - NRC Meeting, 1984 Dec. (Box 56)
  - NRC Meeting, 1984 Nov. (Box 56)
  - Nuclear Industry, 1983 May (Box 56)
  - Revised Minutes of April 25-26, 1984 (Box 56)
  - NSRG Meeting, 1984 Jul. 5 (Box 56)
  - Statements of Nunzio J. Palladino and Steven C. Griffith, Jr., 1984 Jun. (Box 56)
  - NRC Meeting, 1984 Aug. 27 (Box 56)
  - Operating License Risks, undated (Box 56)
  - The Price-Anderson Act, 1984 Mar. (Box 56)
  - The Effects of Ionizing Radiation on Human Health, 1984 Jan. (Box 56)
  - Review of Nuclear Liability Compensation Systems Applicable to Reactors Outside the United States, 1983 Nov. (Box 56)
  - Financial Protection Against Nuclear Hazards, 1984 Jan. 19 (Box 56)
  - The Nuclear Liability Claim Experience of the Nuclear Insurance Pools, 1984 Jan. (Box 56)
  - NRC, 1983-1984 (Box 56)
  - Independent Review and Audit Group (IRAG), 1983 May 24 (Box 56)
  - Fermi-Wolverine Power Supply Cooperative (PSC) 1983-1984 (Box 56)
  - BNRC, 1984 Mar. 26 (Box 56)
  - Nuclear Review Committee, 1984 (Box 56)
  - Minutes of NSRG Meeting, 1984 Oct. 17-18 (Box 56)
  - NSRG, 1984 Jul. (Box 56)
  - NSRG, 1983-1984 (Box 56)
  - Nuclear Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 56)
  - IRAG, 1983 (Box 56)
  - Nuclear Background Briefing Report for the Board Nuclear Review Committee, 1983 Oct. 18 (volume) (Box 56)
  - NRC Trip, 1982-1984 (Box 56)
  - Presentation to the Board of Directors, 1985 Mar. (Box 56)
  - NRC Meeting, 1985 Sept., 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Minutes of NSRG Meeting on May 29, 1984; 1984 June 20 (Box 57)
  - The Detroit Edison Company Case Number U-7660 Direct Testimony and Exhibits, 1987 May, 7 folders (Box 57)
- Fermi Awards Series, 1987-1989
  Consists of letters of nominations for the 1989 Fermi Award which the ERAB gives to recognize those who contributed significantly to the energy field. Roddis served as a member of the screening panel.
  - Table of Contents- Robert Brent, 1987-1989 (Box 57)
  - Leo Brewer- John Dawson, 1987-1989 (Box 57)
  - Ersel Evans- Bertrand Goldschmidt, 1987-1989 (Box 57)
  - Wolf Haefele- Frank Kruesi, 1987-1989 (Box 57)
  - Raymond Latarjet- Walter Marshall, 1987-1989 (Box 57)
  - Roger McClellan- Takashi Mukaibo, 1987-1989 (Box 57)
  - James Neel- David Okrent, 1987-1989 (Box 58)
  - Donato Palumbo- Tulito Regge, 1987-1989 (Box 58)
  - Fred Reines- John Schiffer, 1987-1989 (Box 58)
  - James Schlesinger- Charles Slitcher, 1987-1989 (Box 58)
  - Newell Stannard- Cornelius Tobius, 1987-1989 (Box 58)
  - Anthony Turkerich- Bruno Zumino, 1987-1989 (Box 58)
- Puerto Rico Water Resource Authority (PRWRA), 1976-1982 and undated
  The PRWRA controls Puerto Rico's water supply. Materials include correspondence, data, memoranda, congressional memoranda, member lists, notes, graphs, charts, monthly reports, reports, articles, and clippings. Isuues discussed include alternative energy sources (hydroelectric and photovollar sources), energy conservation, the economic prospects of the commonwealth, ocean thermal energy, and the refining and petrochemical industries located on the island.
  - Data, 1978-1979 (Box 58)
  - Puerto Rican Business Supplements, 1978-1982 (Box 58)
  - Overview of the Puerto Rican Economy, 1950-1979 (Box 58)
  - Ocean Thermal Energy Conversion, 1978 Dec. (Box 58)
  - Island Strategy for OTEC Commercialization, 1978-1979 (Box 58)
  - Burns and Roe Report on Electrical Cogeneration in Puerto Rico, 1979 Sept. 12 (Box 58)
  - National Academy of Science Puerto Rico Report, 1978-1979 (Box 58)
  - Final Draft Report on Photovoltaic Potential in Puerto Rico, 1979 Aug. (Box 58)
  - Long-Term Projectionss of the Puerto Rican Economy, 1979 July (Box 58)
  - Information for Electrical Utility System Subcommittee No. 1, 1979 July 17 (Box 58)
  - Committee Meeting on Puerto Rico's Future Energy Alternatives, 1978 Dec. 13-15 (Box 58)
  - Committee Meeting on Puerto Rico's Future Energy Alternatives, 1979 Feb. 13 (Box 58)
  - Correspondence Involving the National Research Council, 1979 Jan. (Box 58)
  - Committee Meeting on Puerto Rico's Future Energy Alternatives, 1979 Mar. 14 (Box 58)
  - Future Energy Alternatives - Interim Report Draft, 1979 Apr. 20 (Box 58)
  - Committee Meeting on Puerto Rico's Future Energy Alternatives, 1979 Apr. 17 (Box 58)
  - Committee on Future Energy Alternatives for Puerto Rico, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Initial Committee Meeting on Puerto Rico's Future Energy Alternatives, 1978 Nov. 28 (Box 58)
  - Committee Meeting on Puerto Rico's Future Energy Alternatives, 1979 Aug. 6-9 (Box 58)
  - Committee Meeting on Puerto Rico's Future Energy Alternatives, 1979 Oct. 24-26 (Box 58)
  - Puerto Rico Water Resource Authority Bond Information, 1978 Oct.1 (Box 58)
  - National Research Council Committee On Natural Resources Energy Board, 1977-1979 (Box 58)
  - Puerto Rico Water Resources Authority Monthly Report, 1977 Oct. (Box 58)
  - Puerto Rico Water Resource Authority, 1977-1979 (Box 59)
  - Puerto Rico Water Resource Authority Production Division Monthly Report, 1978 Aug. (Box 59)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 59)
  - National Academy of Science Puerto Rican Activities, 1979 (Box 59)
  - Puerto Rican Hydoelectric Materials, 1979 (Box 59)
  - Puerto Rico Hydroelectricity, 1978-1979 (Box 59)
  - Technical Appendix on Hydroelectric Potential, undated (Box 59)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 59)
  - Puerto Rican Energy Manuals, 1978 (Box 59)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 59)
  - Briefing Memorandum on International Business, 1978 Nov. 12-15 (Box 59)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 59)
  - Chapter Two of Energy and the Puerto Rican Economy, undated (Box 59)
  - Report from Standard and Poor on the Economic Prospects of Puerto Rico, 1978 Nov. 16 (Box 59)
  - Donovan, Hamester, and Rattien, Inc. Report on Energy Data in Puerto Rico, 1979 (Box 59)
  - Puerto Rico Water Resources Authority Briefing Presentation, 1978 Nov. 28 (Box 59)
  - Puerto Rico Water Resource Authority Annual Generation Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 59)
  - Puerto Rico Water Resource Authority Power Production Reports, 1976-1978 (Box 59)
  - Refining and Petrochemicals in Puerto Rico, 1979 Jan. (Box 59)
  - Puerto Rico Office of Energy Comments on Refining Industry, 1979 Jan. 31 (Box 59)
  - Puerto Rico Office of Energy Report on Energy and the Puerto Rican Economy, undated (Box 59)
  - Puerto Rico Water Resource Authority Response to the National Research Council, 1979 Jan. 26 (Box 59)
  - North Coast Nuclear Plant Report, 1977 Mar. (Box 59)
  - Puerto Rico Water Resource Authority Sales and Revenue Forecast, 1977-1978 and 1981-1982 (Box 59)
- Intenational Nuclear Energy Systems Company (INESCO), 1977-1985 and undated
  Roddis was on the board and a shareholder of INESCO. This series includes correspondence, reports, articles, memoranda, clippings, testimonies, brochures, annual reports, photographs, notes, speeches, and INESCO Board of Directors meetings' minutes and agendas. Topics include nuclear fusion as a viable energy source; evaluations of surveillance systems for nuclear power plants, shareholder information, financial projections for INESCO, and the production of robotics to aid in parts of the nuclear process when humans cannot.
  - Automated Technology Corporation Board of Directors Meeting, 1985 Oct. 14 (Box 59)
  - Advanced Resource Development Capability Statement, 1982 Sept. (Box 59)
  - Correspondence, 1983 May 16 (Box 59)
  - EPRI NDE Center Trip Report, 1983 Oct. 12 (Box 59)
  - Industrial Remote Inspection System (IRIS) Business Plan, 1983 (Box 59)
  - Analysis & Technology Inc. (A&T) Brochures, 1982 and 1984 (Box 59)
  - A&T Package, 1983 Feb. 25 (Box 59)
  - A&T Package, 1983 Feb. 22 (Box 59)
  - A&T Materials, 1983 Mar. 1 (Box 59)
  - Advanced Resource Development, Inc. Profile and Future Directions, undated (Box 59)
  - Draft of Iris Business Plan, undated (Box 59)
  - Correspondence, 1978 Jun. 7-8 (Box 59)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - Aviation Week Fusion Article, 1978 Jun. 12 (Box 60)
  - Articles and Clippings Concerning Nuclear Power, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
  - INESCO Shareholder Meeting Transcript, 1983 May 14 (Box 60)
  - INESCO, 1984 (Box 60)
  - INESCO, 1983 (Box 60)
  - INESCO, 1982 (Box 60)
  - INESCO- Boeing, 1982 (Box 60)
  - Announcement of Shareholder Meeting for the Corporation, 1984 Jan. 13 (Box 60)
  - Declaration of Mr. Louis H. Roddis, Jr., 1983 Sept. 23 (Box 60)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 60)
  - Written Statement fo R.W. Bussard, 1978 Feb. 20 (Box 60)
  - Proposal for Proof-of-Principle (POP) Fusion Physics Ignition and Burn Experiments (PHIBEX) by INESCO, 1977 Dec. 15 (Box 60)
  - Written Testimony of Robert Bussard Magnetic Fusion Energy, 1978 Feb. 7 (Box 60)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 60)
  - Meeting on INESCO Aggressive Experiment Physics Issues, 1977 Dec. 21 (Box 60)
  - Proposal for Low-Cost Fusion Power Systems, 1977 Jan. 13 (Box 60)
  - INESCO, 1977-1979 (Box 60)
  - INESCO Change of Address Announcement, 1979 Sept. 27 (Box 60)
  - INESCO Shareholder Agreement and Other Materials, 1979 (Box 60)
  - Roddis Trip Report to Bussard, 1979 Feb. 2 (Box 60)
  - Bussard Correspondence with Hirsch, 1977 Dec. 5 (Box 60)
  - Fusion Related Advanced Energy Systems Study, 1979 Mar. 2 (3 volumes) (Box 60)
  - INESCO Balance Sheet, 1977 Nov. 30 (Box 60)
  - Proposal for POP Fusion PHIBEX by INESCO, 1977 Dec. 5, 2 folders (Box 60)
- Committee on Nuclear and Alternative Energy Systems (CONAES) 1976-1977
  CONAES is a part of the National Review Committee (NRC) of the National Academy of Sciences and National Academy of Engineering. Its purpose is to study the role of nuclear power among alternative energy systems for the years 1980 through 2010 with consideration on not only supply of this energy but also demand. This series contains correspondence, memoranda, articles, figures, reports, and charts. Issues discussed range from nuclear fission to the selection of research and development programs for assured future energy supplies.
  - Committe on Nuclear and Alternative Energy Systems Fuel Cycle, 1976 (Box 60)
  - CONAES Report and Drafts, 1977 (Box 60)
  - CONAES Alt. Converters, 1977 (Box 60)
  - Alt. Converters Panel, 1976 Dec. 13 (Box 60)
  - Washington, 1976 Aug. 16 (Box 61)
- Energy Research and Development Administration (ERDA) 1977-1978 and undated
  ERDA is largely focussed on the formulation and implementation of effective research, development, and demonstration plans capable of meeting national energy needs. This seies contains correspondence, memoranda, clippings, speeches, studies, meeting summary transcripts, and reports. The main issue discussed in the series is the connection between government and the private sector in energy production.
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 61)
  - Speech by Donald Beattie, 1977 Mar. 9 (Box 61)
  - Energy Research and Development Administration Meeting, 1977 Jan. 25 (Box 61)
  - Private Sector Participation Study, undated (Box 61)
  - Commission on Natural Resources Board on Energy Studies, 1977 (Box 61)
  - Study of the Private Sector Participation in the Planning of Government Supported Energy Research, Development, and Demonstration, 1977 (Box 61)
  - Meeting of Committee on Energy Research, Development, and Demonstration Planning, 1978 Jan. 20, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Nuclear Technology Background Paper, 1977 July 1 (Box 61)
  - Committee on Private Sector Participation in Government Energy Research, Development, and Demonstration Project Planning, 1977 June 2 (Box 61)
  - Summary and Transcript of Research, Development, and Demonstration Meeting, 1977 July 12-13, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Government Nuclear Technology Planning--Industrial View, 1977 June 2 (Box 61)
  - Correspondence, 1977 Apr. 21 (Box 61)
  - Task Statement for Committee Sub-Group Background Papers, undated (Box 61)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 61)
  - Transcript from Second Meeting of Committee on Private Sector Participation in Government Energy Research, Development, and Demonstration Planning, 1977 April 1 (Box 61)
  - Transcript of Meeting by Committee on Private Sector Participation in Government Energy Research, Development, and Demonstration Planning, 1977 Mar. 9 (Box 61)
  - Energy Research, Development, and Demonstration Meeting, 1977 Jul. 12-13, 2 folders (Box 61)
- Exxon, 1979-1980
  Contains correspondence, reports, memoranda, notes, tables, charts, illustrations, brochures, printed materials, and graphs. This series concerns the production of energy by coal and oil conversion processes, disposal of the conversion processes' wastes,dentrifications, and other particle removal. Roddis worked as a consultant to Exxon's research and development department in order to aid them in making technological advances in these areas.
  - Consolidated Edison, 1979 June 6 (Box 61)
  - Exxon TVA, 1979 (Box 61)
  - Exxon--Keystone, 1979 (Box 61)
  - Exxon--Southern California Edison, 1979 (Box 61)
  - Exxon, 1979 Apr. 2-4 (Box 61)
  - Exxon--Denitrification, 1979 May 5 (Box 61)
  - Exxon-- Los Angeles Department of Water and Power, 1979 May 22 (Box 61)
  - Exxon--Denitrification, 1979 Apr. 30 (Box 61)
  - Exxon, 1978 (Box 61)
  - Evaluation of the Thermal Denitrification Market Potential, 1979 Apr. (Box 61)
  - Exxon--TVA, 1979 Oct. 2 (Box 61)
  - Exxon--Research and Development, 1979 Oct. 11 (Box 61)
  - Exxon Materials, 1979 Aug. 27 and Sept. 14 (Box 61)
  - Exxon-EPRI, 1979 Sept. 18 (Box 61)
  - Thermal Denitrification Market Evaluation, 1979 Apr. 19 (Box 61)
  - Exxon R&E, 1979 Apr. 18-19 New York Times Magazine, 1980 Aug. 3 (Box 61)
  - Application of the Exxon Magnetically Stabilized Bed Process to Utility Boilers--A Comparative Economic Evaluation, 1980 Jan. (Box 62)
  - Exxon--Florham Park, 1979 Oct. 16 (Box 62)
  - Exxon--Simulators, 1980 June 15 (Box 62)
- J. V. Neely Nuclear Power Consultants, 1976-1978 and undated
  Contains correspondence, memoranda, notes, trip and financial reports, Board of Directors meeting minutes and press releases. This series discusses the company's marketing strategies, quality assurance programs, and Roddis'ss becoming a member of the Board of Directors of this newly established consulting firm.
  - J.V. Neely Corporate, 1977 Mar. (Box 62)
  - J.V. Neely-General Public Utilities Proposals, 1977 Feb. (Box 62)
  - J.V. Neely Meetings, 1976-1978 (Box 62)
  - J.V. Neely Brochures, 1976 Nov. (Box 62)
  - J.V. Neely Brochures, undated (Box 62)
- Gould, 1973-1986 and undated
  Consists of correspondence, memoranda, financial, operating, trip, annual, and management reports, board meeting minutes and agendas, notes, news releases, charts, brochures, sketches, articles, and clippings. Gould is a major international developer and manufacturer of electrical and electronic products. Roddis served on its Board of Directors. Issues include electromechanics, electrochemistry, electronics, load management, underwater gas cable systems, solar power, metallurgy, research and defense systems, batteries, torpedos, and submarines.
  - I-T-E Imperial, 1973-1975, 3 folders (Box 62)
  - Memorandum on Load Leveling, 1976 Sept. 15 (Box 62)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 62)
  - Gould Scientific Advisory Board, 1978 June 14 (Box 62)
  - Scientific Advisory Board Load Management, 1978 (Box 62)
  - Gould Board of Directors Meeting, 1978 Jan. 24 (Box 62)
  - Lawrence Livermore Laboratory--Electric Vehicle, 1978 Apr. 28 (Box 62)
  - Institute of Gas Technology--Munters Environmental Control System --Solar Air Conditioning and Heat, 1973-1977 (Box 62)
  - Gould-- Con Edison, 1977 Jan. 20 (Box 62)
  - Gould Wanser Trip Materials, 1976-1977 (Box 62)
  - Gould Scientific Advisory Board Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 62)
  - Gould Load Leveling, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Gould Press Releases, 1976 (Box 62)
  - Multiplex, undated (Box 62)
  - TVA Electric Vehicle, 1978 (Box 62)
  - Scientific Advisory Council, 1980 Jul. 25 (Box 62)
  - Scientific Advisory Council Meeting Minutes, 1980 July 25 (Box 62)
  - Special Mission Submarine, 1979 (Box 62)
  - Scientific Advisory Board Meeting, 1979 June 26 (Box 62)
  - Scientific Advisory Board, 1979 Sept. 11 (Box 62)
  - Scientific Advisory Board, 1979 Dec. 6 (Box 62)
  - Thinwall Energy Audit, 1979 Nov. 1 (Box 62)
  - Managing Technical Development for Profit, 1980 Jan. (Box 62)
  - Gould--Energy Consulting, 1979 (Box 62)
  - Gould-- Cleveland, 1980 Jan. 19 (Box 62)
  - Correspondence with Gibbs, 1980 Jan. 28 (Box 62)
  - Correspondence, 1980 Jan. 31 (Box 62)
  - Scientific Advisory Board, 1978 Sept. 20 (Box 62)
  - Gould--Brown Boveri, 1977 Aug. 18 (Box 62)
  - United Technologies Corporation, 1977 Sept. 9 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Board, 1978 Apr. 15 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Board Meeting, 1978 Dec. 6 (Box 63)
  - Putting the Energy Puzzle Together, 1979 Feb. 12 (Box 63)
  - Correspondence, 1978 Sept. 25 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Board, 1979 (Box 63)
  - Bob Pry's Report on Battery Powered Surveillance Submarines, 1979-1980 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Board Meeting, 1977 Dec. 13 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Board, 1976 Dec. 13 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Board, 1977 (Box 63)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Board, 1980 Oct. 12 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Council Meeting, 1980 Dec. 8 (Box 63)
  - Gould Simulators, 1980 (Box 63)
  - Government Systems Division, 1981 July 1 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Council -- Andover, Md. 1981 June 8 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Council, 1981 Feb. 16 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Council-- Cleveland, Oh. 1981 Oct. 16 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Council, 1981 Dec. 1 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Council, 1982 Mar. 15 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Council, 1982 Sept. 1 (Box 63)
  - Scientific Advisory Council--Education, 1982 Nov. 30 (Box 63)
  - Gould Annual Report, 1981 (Box 63)
  - Kabelmetal Materials, 1976 (Box 63)
  - Gould Cable Market Study, 1976-1977 (Box 63)
  - Gas Cable Trip Reports, 1977 (Box 63)
  - SF6 Cable Trip Reports, Rough Drafts, 1977 Mar. (Box 63)
  - Gould Annual Report, 1982 (Box 63)
  - Notice of Annual Meeting of Gould, Inc. Stockholders, 1982 May 5 (Box 63)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 63)
  - Graphnet Faxgram, 1983 Mar. 29 (Box 63)
  - Gould, Inc. Board of Directors Meeting, 1983 Mar. 10 (Box 63)
  - Gould Management Control Reports, 1982 Dec. (Box 63)
  - Gould Operating Boards Materials, 1983 Jan. (Box 63)
  - Gould Preliminary Corporate Calendar, 1983 (Box 63)
  - Gould Government Systems, 1982 (Box 63)
  - Visit Schedule for Roddis to Gould, Inc., 1983 July 13 (Box 63)
  - Guerri Resume, 1983 May 12 (Box 64)
  - Gould Government Systems Board, 1983 (Box 64)
  - Gould Information Update for Research and Defense Systems, 1983 June 15 (Box 64)
  - Gould Business Forecasts and Past Information, 1983 (Box 64)
  - Visit Schedule for Roddis to Gould, 1983 Jul. 19 (Box 64)
  - Gould Research on Advanced Materials, undated (Box 64)
  - Research and Defense Systems Operating Board Meeting, 1983 July 20 (Box 64)
  - German Article on American Electronic Microsystems, 1983 (Box 64)
  - Gould, Inc. Board of Directors Meeting, 1983 Mar. 10-11 (Box 64)
  - Gould Management Control Report, 1983 Feb. (Box 64)
  - Gould Management Control Report, 1983 Mar. (Box 64)
  - Gould Stock Information, 1983 (Box 64)
  - Gould Management Control Report, 1983 Apr. (Box 64)
  - Gould, Inc. Board of Directors Meeting, 1983 May 2-3 (Box 64)
  - Gould Management Control Report, 1983 May (Box 64)
  - Wood Gundy Report on Gould, 1983 June 21 (Box 64)
  - L.F. Rothschild Investor Presentation, 1983 May 25 (Box 64)
  - Gould Research and Defense Systems, 1983 Feb. 1 (Box 64)
  - Gould Defense Electronics Division, undated (Box 64)
  - Correspondence, 1983 July 29 (Box 64)
  - Gould, Inc. Board of Directors Meeting, 1983 July 19 (Box 64)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 64)
  - Gould in Europe, 1983 (Box 64)
  - Gould Management Control Report, 1983 July (Box 64)
  - Gould, Inc. Board of Directors Meeting, 1983 Sept. 20 (Box 64)
  - Results of Pre-Acquisition Study of Dexcel, Inc. 1983 Jan. 25 (Box 64)
  - Gould Management Control Report, 1983 Jan. (Box 64)
  - Consent in Lieu for Gould Defense Systems, Inc. Meeting of Board of Directors, 1985 Feb. 23 (Box 64)
  - Gould, Inc. Nominating Committee Meeting, 1983 Jan. 25 (Box 64)
  - Gould, Inc. Board of Directors Meeting, 1983 Jan. 25 (Box 64)
  - Gould, Inc. Foil Plant in South Carolina, 1982 Dec. (Box 64)
  - Hilton Head Trip for Annual Review of Defense Systems Group, 1983 May 18-22 (Box 64)
  - Gould Defense Group, 1982 (Box 64)
  - Gould Management Control Reports, 1983 Aug. (Box 64)
  - Gould Management Control Reports, 1983 June (Box 64)
  - Advanced Technology Center (ATC), 1983 (Box 64)
  - GGS Operating Board, 1984 Feb. 13 (Box 64)
  - Defense Systems Business Section Operating Board Meeting, 1984 Aug. 21 (Box 64)
  - Ocean Systems Division Meeting, 1984 Aug. 29 (Box 65)
  - Gould, Inc. Defense Systems Newsletter, 1984 Aug. (Box 65)
  - Inter-Office Memoranda, 1983-1984 (Box 65)
  - Research and Defense Systems Operating Board Manual, 1983 (Box 65)
  - Special Project, 1981 Nov. 29 (Box 65)
  - Gould Defense Systems Operating Board Meeting, 1983 Nov. 15 (Box 65)
  - Correspondence, 1984 Jan. 11 (Box 65)
  - Gould Research Center 1985-1989 (Box 65)
  - Strategic Plan, 1984 May (Box 65)
  - Operating Board Meeting Minutes, 1983 Nov. 15 (Box 65)
  - NavCom, 1984 Jan. 11 (Box 65)
  - Gould Defense Systems Longboat Key Conference, 1985 Mar. 20-22 (Box 65)
  - Gould, Inc. Systems Protection Divisionand Gould, Inc. Systems and Simulation Division, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Gould Defense Systems Operating Board Meetings, 1984 Aug. 21 and Oct. 17 (Box 65)